JACK FLETCHER

4 Raps Green, Taunton Somerset · 07502868409

dev@jack-fletcher.me https://www.linkedin.com/in/-jack-fletcher https://jack-fletcher.me/

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A versatile graduate with an interest in all facets of technology, with a commitment to designing and developing innovative solutions for a problem domain.

I have experience with object orientated programming using an iterative approach.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C# (Three years), Python (6 Months) HTML/CSS (6 months)

Software Experience: Windows 10, Ubuntu Linux, Visual Studio 2017/2019, Docker, Microsoft Remote Desktop, MATLAB, Unity Engine, PyCharm, Visual Studio Code, Hyper-V, VirtualBox

Other: I have experience working as a programmer in an agile environment of two to three developers in an academic setting, leading projects to completion as either the project lead or the technical lead. I have experience working with interdisciplinary teams and conveying complex ideas to non-technical teams.

EXPERIENCE

2020-2021

Implementation Consultant

Synertec

I worked full time as an Implementation Consultant at Synertec. I used a proprietary programming language to develop routing rules and developed visuals for customer's documents based on customer requirements and continuous feedback. In addition to this, I liaised with other technical and non-technical teams to iterate on our products and development practices.

2016-2018

General Assistant

Primark

I worked part time as a general assistant for four to eight hours a week on weekends. As a general assistant I minimized customer complaints by providing exemplary service. In addition to this, I maximised sales by ensuring the shop floor was fully stocked.

PROJECTS

JANUARY 2022 - MAY 2022

RuneCom

Technology Stack: JavaScript, React Native, CSS

A mobile application built in JavaScript using React Native. Using community feedback, it consolidated useful game information to enhance the users experience during gameplay. Published on the Play Store and is currently in public testing through TestFlight.

JUNE 2020 - ONGOING

Pybot

Technology Stack: Python, Discord.Py

A Discord bot written in Python, that scrapes user data from a given website and displays it in a user-friendly way. Uses a local SQLite database to store user information, which can allow users to subscribe to daily notifications.

JANUARY 2020- MAY 2020

Necromancer Game VR

Technology Stack: C#, XML, Unity

A 3D Tower Defence style game, where you take control of a necromancer developing an army. As a solo project completed in a single semester, I managed the project and developed all game systems. I gained knowledge in development practices for VR and was able to ascertain different interactions with emergent technologies.

JANUARY 2019- APRIL 2019

PEC-Application

Technology Stack: C#, Unity

A 2D simulation created in Unity created in partnership with Plymouth Energy Community that aimed to prototype a tool that could be used alongside home visits from PEC agents, to better visualize the effects their actions have on damp and mould within their home.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2023

Computer Science (MSc), Part-time

Staffordshire University

2016-2020

Computing & Games Development (BSc), Full-time

University of Plymouth

Graduated with a 2:1 / Second Class; First Division

Courses Completed:

- Web Game Technologies
- Games Development Immersive
- Software Engineering
- Games Workshop
- Intelligent Systems
- Algorithms, Data Structures and Mathematics
- Computation Theory and Artificial Intelligence

- Interactive Systems Workshop
- Artificial Intelligence for Game Development
- Object-oriented Software Engineering with Design Patterns
- Machine Learning
- Industry Engagement
- Programming for Entertainment Systems

2011-2013

A Levels: English Literature & Language, Psychology, Classic Civilisation

Richard Huish College

ACTIVITIES

• Took part in Jamfuser 2020 as part of a team, creating all game systems and leading development in 'Pose of Faith'.